<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bores</title>
    <link>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bores</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 10:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://coffee-fueled.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Attack Scenario: Phishing to Ransom</title>
      <link>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/resources/phishing_scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 10:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/resources/phishing_scenario/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is an attack scenario designed to support incident response and investigation tabletop exercises. Mitigations and detection possibilities are called out at each stage, so you can begin the exercise at any point in the narrative. Whether you then use the previous actions to provide additional context and highlight gaps in detection, or continue the scenario on depending on the actions and responses of participants, is entirely up to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doorstep Dispensary</title>
      <link>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/blog/doorstep_dispensaree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 12:22:40 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/blog/doorstep_dispensaree/</guid>
      <description>Doorstep Dispensaree There are a few lessons to pull out of this case, but for those who want to look at the details themselves the full ICO penalty notice is available from their website.
The ICO identified a number of failings after they were called in by the MHRA, who had found some curious containers while executing a search warrant for their own investigation. In a courtyard behind the premises they found:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffee-fueled.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>